https://www.penfed.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | PenFed Credit Union
We use cookies to provide you with better experiences and allow you to navigate our website. By clicking “I ACCEPT”, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with our Privacy, GDPR and Cookie Policies.
I ACCEPT
I Do Not Accept
Login
Search
Routing #
256078446
Partners
Member Discounts
All IRAs
How Can We Help?
Contact Us
FAQs
Forms
Advice Center
Special
CREDIT CARDS
Our Cards
Cards Overview
Tools & More
Reward Redemptions
Card Resource Center
Debt Protection
How Can We Help?
Contact Us
FAQs
Forms
Advice Center
Special
Auto
Auto Loans
Auto Loan Overview
Mechanical Breakdown Protection
Guaranteed Asset Protection (GAP)
Debt Protection
How Can We Help?
Contact Us
FAQs
Forms
Advice Center
Special
Mortgage & Home Equity
Mortgages
Mortgage Center
PenFed Title, LLC
How Can We Help?
Contact PenFed Mortgage Team
FAQs
Forms
Advice Center
Special
Loans
Personal Loans
Personal Loans
Personal Line of Credit
Student Loans
Student Loan Refinancing
In-School Student Loans
How Can We Help?
Contact Us
FAQs
Forms
Advice Center
Special
Learn
Learning Hub
Learning Center
Debt Protection
HOW CAN WE HELP?
Media & PR Center
Careers
Stories
Contact Us
Special
Join Now
Log In
Resources
Affinity Title
Get Started
×
Please enter a valid username.
LOGIN
First time logging in?
Set up your Online Login
JOIN
Policy, Forms, & Disclosures.
PRIVACY POLICY
We're committed to maintaining your privacy & trust.
PENFED PRIVACY POLICY
Keeping your personal information safe is our priority.
Find out how we collect, use, share, and protect information about you below or:
Download Privacy Policy PDF (English)
Download Privacy Policy PDF (Spanish)
WHY?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
WHAT?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or services you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and account balances
Credit history and payment history
Transaction history and overdraft history
HOW?
All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. Read the section below to learn why financial companies share their members’ personal information, why PenFed chooses to share, and whether you can limit this sharing.
REASONS WE CAN SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
DOES PENFED SHARE THIS INFORMATION?
CAN I LIMIT SHARING?
For our everyday business purposes—such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders, and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus.
No
For our marketing purposes—to offer our products and services to you
Yes
For joint marketing with other financial institutions
No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes—information about your transactions and experiences
No
We Don't Share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
No
We Don't Share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
Yes
In order to limit our sharing or if you have any questions, please call: 800-247-5626
Except for cookies, if you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice.
When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
If you wish to adjust your browser settings to block cookies, please see our Cookie Policy to learn more: https://www.penfed.org/cookie-policy
1. Who is providing this notice?
PenFed.
2. How does PenFed protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
3. How does PenFed collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
Open an account or deposit money
Pay your bills or apply for a loan
Use your credit or debit card
Browse our website
4. Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness.
Affiliates from using your information to market to you.
Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.
5. What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
DEFINITIONS
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
PenFed does not share with our affiliates
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Nonaffiliated companies we share with can include insurance companies, direct marketing companies, non-profit organizations, and credit card networks.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include investments, insurance, and credit card companies
ALL PRODUCTS
LEARN
MEMBERSHIP
Mortgage
Auto Loans
Credit Cards
Checking
Personal Loans
BROWSE ALL PRODUCTS
Locations
Careers
Stories
Foundation
Contact
This credit union is federally insured by the National Credit Union Administration. Rates are current as of  unless otherwise noted and are subject to change.
APY = Annual Percentage Yield
APR = Annual Percentage Rate
Pentagon Federal Credit Union
Routing # 256078446
© Pentagon Federal Credit Union
PRIVACY POLICY
SECURITY CENTER
SERVICE FEES
USERNAME
Please enter a valid username.
LOGIN
I need help logging in
Having Troubles?
Forgot Username
Forgot Password
Forgot Username and Password
Unlock Account
First time logging in?
Create an online account
Not yet a member?
Become a member and take advantage of products and exclusive offers!
Join Now
Car Buying Service
Don't overpay for your next car
Search for Cars
×
IMPORTANT NOTICE
You are leaving PenFed.org and entering
a third party Website that is not a part of Pentagon Federal Credit Union.
The content you are about to view is produced by a third party unaffiliated to Pentagon Federal Credit Union. PenFed takes no responsibility for the content of the page.
IMPORTANT NOTICE
You are leaving PenFed.org and entering
a third party site. PenFed Realty, LLC is wholly owned by PenFed and this referral may provide PenFed a financial or other benefit.
For more information about the relationship between PenFed and PenFed Realty, LLC, see the Affiliate Business Arrangement Disclosure.
IMPORTANT NOTICE
You are leaving PenFed.org and entering
a third party site. PenFed Title, LLC is wholly owned by PenFed and this referral may provide PenFed a financial or other benefit.
For more information about the relationship between PenFed and PenFed Title, LLC, see the Affiliate Business Arrangement Disclosure.
CONTINUE
OR CANCEL
